<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <option name="newTranslationDialogWidth" value="594" />
    <option name="newTranslationDialogX" value="1095" />
    <option name="newTranslationDialogY" value="618" />
    <histories>
      <item value="This does not seem to be a WordPress installation." />
      <item value="Please check and update plugin UCO - Auctions to version 1.9.4.12. Bidspirit has made important changes to the APIs we've added in this release." />
      <item value="Bidspirit has made important changes to the APIs we've added in this release." />
      <item value="Bidspirit внёс важные изменения в API которые мы добавили в этой версии." />
      <item value="Please check and update plugin UCO - Auctions to version 1.9.4.12." />
      <item value="Please check and update plugin UCO - Auctions from version 1.9.4.12." />
      <item value="Пожалуйста, предоставьте мне ftp доступ к сайту." />
      <item value="Elementor interrupts the plugin and takes over the page template that is designed for the plugin page." />
      <item value="Elementor перебивает плагин и забирает на себя шаблон страницы которая расчитана для страницы плагина." />
      <item value="I see the problem, but haven't figured out how to fix it yet" />
      <item value="Проблему я вижу, но пока не определил как её исправить" />
      <item value="You have a lot of links to this site:" />
      <item value="У вас очень много ссылок на этот сайт:" />
      <item value="You have very a lot link on this site:" />
      <item value="You have very a lot" />
      <item value="Мы рекомендуем включить синхронизацию на стороне сервера с помощью cron." />
      <item value="We recommend enable sync on server side help cron." />
      <item value="Today we will start updating the plugin for all clients." />
      <item value="Сегодня начанём обновлять у всех клиентов плагин." />
      <item value="Phone code" />
      <item value="clients don't placed on us server" />
      <item value="clients placed on us server" />
      <item value="clients when placed on us server" />
      <item value="Task splited on subtasks" />
      <item value="Split on subtasks" />
      <item value="We did estimate for task &quot;Changes in phones&quot;." />
      <item value="Some auction houses require id and or tax number from a user that wants to participate in their auctions. These requirement may be different if a user is from the same country as the auction house or is from a foreign country, and if the user is a company (i.e. this company field is not empty). use this api when you need to decide which information to force when you collecting information fo the usersupdateDetails api" />
      <item value="Update hosting clients - 1-hour" />
      <item value="Code changes and QA - 4 hours Update hosting clients - 1 hour Update plugin client - 1-3 hours" />
      <item value="Hi, There are few new developments in high priority that we need: Use country code in the phone number: We started to display the phone number in 2 fields: country code and the phone number. The field mobilePhone is going to be deprecated and instead the fields phoneCountryCode + phone need to be used. In order to get all values for phoneCountryCode - use the settingsgetCountriesList. Everything is described in the updated updated API document. Check the updated demo to see how to display and update the phone field In the next phase we will handle phone verification, currently there is no need. Registration per auction with a credit cards: We added an option to register to an auction with a credit card. I made the settings to auction 10 in the QA. You will see that there are 2 new menus for each auction in the admin: Approval requests and Approved participants. Each approved user is added to the Approved participants of the relevant auction. You can find the information in the API document at sections Approval per auction and Working with payment methods. And you can see in the demo the exact implementation. The development should include: A section for the user managing his Payment methods - add and delete (see the demo) When the approval per auction is enabled for a certain auction - add a button to register for the auction. The button opens a registration popup - you can see the implementation in the demo and how we did it in our QA portal. I suggest we will have a short phone call and go over it. Please let me know when you are available." />
      <item value="in Hebrew will look like this" />
      <item value="פתחו את תיבת האוצרות של ההיסטוריה היהודית ופנקו את עצמכם בפיסת היסטוריה." />
      <item value="סיפורים מייצגים" />
      <item value="Hebrew contacts page" />
      <item value="What you mean describe this issue?" />
      <item value="What you mean" />
      <item value="Hebrew Label phone" />
      <item value="He Label phone" />
      <item value="Ask your hosting UDomain what the spf record should be." />
      <item value="Ask your hosting mail what the spf record should be." />
      <item value="Ask your hosting provider what the spf record should be." />
      <item value="Уточните у хостинг провайдера какая должна быть spf запись." />
      <item value="несколько дней" />
      <item value="is More Days" />
      <item value="as slider" />
      <item value="Uncomment when Pro uses the new hook." />
      <item value="We received a message from a Bidpirit Arbel Raz representative that there are problems registering new users in the Google Chrome browser. We will need time to check and find out the reasons." />
      <item value="Мы получили сообщение от представителя Bidpirit Arbel Raz сообщение о том что есть проблемы при регистрации новых пользователей в браузере Google Chrome. Нам потребуется время на проверку и выяснение причин." />
      <item value="Что нового появилось в этом плане?" />
      <item value="We would like to acknowledge that we have received your support request and a ticket has been created. A support representative will be reviewing your request and respond to you as soon as possible. You can review the status of the ticket by logging in to your portal account, or visit the ticket URL: https:support.macincloud.comsupportticketspublic436e177e53eb951db87a05b44b5149c477d4ecc8421e3e386a6f97386cebccc1 If you have not already provided us detailed descriptions and screenshots of the issue you may be experiencing, please reply to this email with those details and relevant screenshots. This will allow us to better exam the issue and help you promptly. Please make sure to provide the specific server name and user name of your server account, as well as contacting us from the original account owner email to prevent support delays. Here are a few tips for common issues. They maybe helpful for you: 1. New Apple App Store submission requirement starts April 25 (reference: https:developer.apple.comnews?id=5zb13auf). If you need to use Xcode 13.x, you should select a plan with macOS Monterey (12.x). If you have a plan with an earlier macOS, please back up your files using a cloud service such as Dropbox.com, Backup and Sync by Google, or other service such as Git, and obtain a new plan with macOS Monterey. The pricing is outlined here: https:checkout.macincloud.comselectmanaged . If you need help, simply confirm that you wish to switch to a newer macOS once you have completed your backup, and we will issue you a new macOS Monterey plan replacing your existing plan. 2. If you are using Visual Studio for Mac and encountering errors regarding the new Xamarin.iOS requirement for Xcode 13.x. Please review topic 1 discussed above. You will need to switch to a newer macOS. 3. If you are encountering app signing issues related to WWDR Certificates, please contact us with your server and account name for assistance. 4. If you are facing server connection issues, please make sure to submit your support request with your server name, user name, and detailed descriptions of the specific error(s) you are encountering. This allows us to quickly identify your server and help you. Please also make sure that you are not behind a home or office firewall that blocks your remote access. 5. If you have not received any new account email with your server access credentials after purchasing a plan, please first check your email SPAM folder. You may find your new account email there. To explore other solutions, you may also visit our Knowledge Base by clicking HERE. To add comments to this support request, you may simply reply to this email. To view the status of the ticket or add online, please login to our Support Portal using the same email that you created the ticket with, or visit: https:support.macincloud.comsupportticketspublic436e177e53eb951db87a05b44b5149c477d4ecc8421e3e386a6f97386cebccc1 Thank you for your patience." />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="1" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="7321" />
        <entry key="ARABIC" value="1" />
        <entry key="AZERBAIJANI" value="4" />
        <entry key="BELARUSIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="BULGARIAN" value="3" />
        <entry key="POLISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="DANISH" value="3" />
        <entry key="GERMAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="RUSSIAN" value="7321" />
        <entry key="FRENCH" value="7" />
        <entry key="FILIPINO" value="1" />
        <entry key="FINNISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="FRISIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="DUTCH" value="3" />
        <entry key="CATALAN" value="3" />
        <entry key="CZECH" value="1" />
        <entry key="CORSICAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="KURDISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="LATIN" value="2" />
        <entry key="LITHUANIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="ROMANIAN" value="8" />
        <entry key="MALTESE" value="1" />
        <entry key="MACEDONIAN" value="3" />
        <entry key="BENGALI" value="1" />
        <entry key="NORWEGIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="PORTUGUESE" value="9" />
        <entry key="SWEDISH" value="9" />
        <entry key="SCOTS_GAELIC" value="1" />
        <entry key="CEBUANO" value="1" />
        <entry key="SOMALI" value="1" />
        <entry key="TELUGU" value="1" />
        <entry key="TURKISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="SPANISH" value="7" />
        <entry key="HEBREW" value="200" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="5" />
        <entry key="HINDI" value="2" />
        <entry key="INDONESIAN" value="4" />
        <entry key="VIETNAMESE" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Cache">
    <option name="lastTrimTime" value="1655894499392" />
  </component>
</application>